{
    "id": "c5bb43c483934fb9820fe3ccca8b6ab9",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………. cleaning the attic, I came across some old photos.",
            "description": "While indicates time. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "While",
                "As soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know any shops ……………………… I can buy used laptops?",
            "description": "Where can mean at which or in which.",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the café ………………………. we used to spend our evenings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "where",
                "here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman …………………………. child was missing seemed hysterical.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. it was a small town, we couldn’t find any hotels there.",
            "description": "As indicates the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks ………………………. she knows everything.",
            "description": "Either as if or as though can be used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. she performed well, she was denied promotion.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. she is very old, she is quite capable of taking care of herself.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… she got the message, she started.",
            "description": "No sooner is used in comparative expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "As long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. she started at 6, she should be here soon.",
            "description": "Either if or as is possible here. If expresses a condition and as expresses the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You can stay with me ………………………….. you want.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "as soon as",
                "as much as",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a question ……………………….. no one could answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}